Please proceed inside. Watch your step.
「どうぞ奥へ
足場に気を付けて」
Where are you taking me?
いったいどこへ連れていくの
What you're about to see is the
brain of this world, as well as its heart.
「今からあなたが目にするのは
この世界の頭脳であり 心臓部でもある場所です」
The heart of the world?
世界の中心
I would like to show
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:死树懒 ASUKA    校对:西西    时间轴:葛蔓     压制：娜夏
Cut open my skull
Look into my head
これほど驚異的な技術によって
I don't know why I'm so harsh
日々の食卓が賄われているというのに
I could be so brash
I'm going to clash
そのことを認識している市民は少な過ぎますね
'Cause I feel
まったく 昨今はどんな科学の恩恵も
I can always show my everything to you
さも当然のことであるかのように享受する連中ばかりでね
If this moment was for me
君のように関心を向けてくれる若者は
I try to hear, lend my ear
本当に珍しいんだよ
Voices inside
嘆かわしいことです
One link to join it all again
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all
So it goes again
#20: Where Justice Lies
The food we eat every day is all thanks to this remarkable technology,
and yet, so many citizens are unaware of it, aren't they?
Indeed. These days, the world is full of people who take the blessings of science for granted.
You don't see many young people like
yourself take an interest in it these days.
I hear that you were a pioneer in
establishing the food system that Japan enjoys today.
現代の日本の食料事情を成立させた立役者をこんなふうに引退させたまま
It's quite regrettable to see you forgotten in your retirement.
放置して一人にしておくなんて
What I'm interested in is the
Uka-no-Mitama defense virus's slipshod security system.
僕が注目しているのはね
ウカノミタマ防御ウイルスの保安体制の杜撰さですよ
Hm?
It may be a benign virus, but it's designed to attack
whatever target is defined in its genetic configuration.
いくら善玉ウイルスとはいえ
シーケンサーへの入力次第で
攻撃対象を任意に変更できるなら
Therefore, it's possible to reconfigure the virus to attack the oats themselves instead of pests.
害虫ではなく
麦そのものを殺すよう調整することも可能だ
Uka-no-Mitama will transform from a god of fertility,
bringing good harvests, to a demon who brings death.
ウカノミタマは収穫をもたらす豊穣の神から
死を運ぶ悪魔へと早変わりする
Wh-What are you...
き…君は…
おまけに　ウイルスの調整と配給を行う管理センターには
On top of that, the control center that handles the configuration and distribution of the virus
閉鎖された旧大学の研究所をそのまま転用しているという
was originally converted from a lab in a closed-down university.
まだサイマティックスキャンによるセキュリティーが実用化される前の施設だ
The facility predates the use of cymatic scans for security.
Its security system uses numeric
passwords or, at best, biometric scans.
保安体制は 暗証番号か生体認証が関の山
これなら曾ての責任者であるあなたの手を借りて
Since you were once in charge there,
I should be able to break in easily with your help.
簡単に突破できますよね
Right, Professor Kudama?
管巻教授
This is the truth behind the Sibyl System. Behind us.
「以上が シビュラシステム
即ち我々についての真相です」
Did Kagari die here?
縢君は…ここで死んだの
あなたたちが殺したの
Did you kill him?
We compared and considered the contributions
Kagari Shuusei would make to society throughout his life
「縢秀星が　生涯を通じて社会に果たす貢献と
against the risk of him revealing the secret of the Sibyl System,
シビュラシステムの機密漏えいの危険を比較検討し
and decided that the risks outweighed the benefits.
後者の方がより重大であると判断しました」
Don't be ridiculous!
ふざけないでよ
Who are you to decide his worth?
何が重大だってのよ
You couldn't even judge Makishima!
槙島を裁けなかった 役立たずのくせに
You're simply useless!
「そのとおり
You are right.
The appearance of criminally asymptomatic people,
whom the Sibyl System cannot analyze, is inevitable.
シビュラシステムがサイコパスを解析できない免罪体質者の発生は
確率的に不可避です」
No matter how intricate and robust a system you build,
「いかに緻密で 堅牢なシステムを構築しようと
a certain number of irregularities
that deviate from it are bound to appear.
必ず　それを逸脱するイレギュラーは一定数で出現します」
And you call that a perfect system?!
完璧なシステムが聞いてあきれるわ
This is the system that decides whether people live or die?
こんなものが人の生き死にを決めてるなんて…
If we simply add to the functionality and complexity of the system, we can never expect it to be perfect.
「ただシステムを改善し 複雑化するだけでは
永遠に完璧さは望めない」
Therefore, we have no choice
「ならば機能ではなく
but to resolve the contradictions by altering the
system's management as opposed to its functionality.
運用の仕方によって 矛盾を解消するしかない」
By permitting the appearance of irregularities
we cannot manage and taking measures to coexist,
「管理しきれないイレギュラーの出現を許容し
共存できる手段を講じることで
the system achieves perfection in a practical sense.
システムは事実上の完璧さを獲得します」
What do you mean by that?
どういうことよ
We can entrust the management of the
system to those who deviate from the system.
「システムを逸脱した者には
システムの運営を委ねればいい」
That is the most logical conclusion.
「これが　最も合理的結論です」
When we used to have individual personalities and bodies,
「我々は 曾て個別の人格と肉体を備えていた頃は
we were all asymptomatic persons who
deviated from the management of the Sibyl System.
いずれもシビュラシステムの管理を逸脱した免罪体質者でした」
In fact, there are many among us who acted far more cruelly than Makishima.
「中には槙島聖護より 遥かに残忍な行為を行った個体も 多数含まれています」
Then are you saying...
じゃあ　シビュラって…
悪人の脳を掻き集めた怪物が
that Sibyl is a monster formed from evil
people's brains that has been running the world?!
この世界を仕切ってたっていうの
「まず初めに 善と悪といった相対的な価値観を排斥することで
In order to establish an absolute system, it is
necessary to reject relative valuations such as "good" or "evil".
All that is needed is a perfect, infallible system.
絶対的なシステムが確立されるのです」
Who manages it and how it is managed are irrelevant.
「必要なのは　完璧にして無謬のシステムそのもの」
「それを　誰がどのように運営するかは問題ではありません」
That's nonsense!
バカ言わないで
「真に完成されたシステムであれば
In a truly perfect system, its operator's will is not questioned.
運用者の意志は問われません」
Our will itself is the system and the
universal standard of value that transcends ethics.
「我々　シビュラの意志そのものがシステムであり
倫理を超越した普遍的価値基準なのです」
Don't be ridiculous!
ふざけないでよ
Just who do you think you are?!
何様のつもりよ
It is true that each and every one of us previously
exhibited numerous problems with our personalities.
「ここにいる各々が 曾ては人格に多くの問題を抱えていたのは事実です」
However, by integrating our minds, we have been
able to operate in harmony, attaining a universal standard.
「だが　全員の精神が統合され 調和することによって
普遍的価値基準を獲得するに至っています」
The more prejudiced and peculiar the
orientations of the individuals who comprise the system,
「むしろ　構成因子となる個体の指向性は偏った特異なものほど
the more new ideas and values they bring to our perception,
我々の認識に新たな着想と価値観をもたらし
and the more flexible and diversified our thinking becomes.
思考をより柔軟で多角的なものへと発展させます」
In that regard, Makishima Shougo's
idiosyncrasy is quite valuable and as such,
「その点において
槙島聖護の特異性は 極めて貴重なケースであり
we have high hopes that he will become an especially useful member.
ひときわ有用な構成員として 期待されます」
We have attained a logical society in which
various contradictions and inequalities are resolved.
「あらゆる矛盾と不公平の解消された合理的社会の実現」
Is that not the ultimate happiness sought by the rational human mind?
「それこそが全ての人類の理性が求める究極の幸福です」
By achieving an absolutely perfect
system, Sibyl has come to embody that ideal.
「完全無欠のシステムとして 完成することにより
シビュラは　その理想を体現する存在となりました」
Why are you telling me all this?
なぜ…そんな話を私に
「今あなたは 我々を生理的に嫌悪し
At this point in time, you detest us
emotionally and hate us instinctively.
感情的に憎悪している」
And yet, you still cannot deny the
Sibyl System's significance and necessity.
「それでも シビュラシステムの有意性と必要性は否定できていない」
「シビュラ無くしては 現在の社会秩序が成立しないという事実を
You accept the fact that the current social
order cannot be maintained without Sibyl.
まず大前提として弁えている」
You value its necessity above its justifiability,
「正当性よりも 必要性に重きを置くあなたの価値基準を
and we highly value your standards.
我々は 高く評価しています」
You killed Kagari in order to keep your secrets!
秘密を守るために縢君まで殺したくせに…
Tsunemori Akane possesses a sense of
purpose that is shared by the Sibyl System.
「常守朱は シビュラシステムと共通の目的意識を備えている」
Hence, we deemed the possibility that you'd reveal
our secrets and endanger the system negligibly small.
「故に　あなたが我々の秘密を暴露して
システムを危険に曝す可能性は 限りなく低いものと判定しました」
Don't treat me like a fool!
なめるんじゃないわよ
You are... You are...!
あんたなんか…
Let me ask you once again.
「再確認しましょう」
Tsunemori Akane, do you wish for a world without the Sibyl System?
「常守朱…　あなたはシビュラシステムのない世界を望みますか」
That's right. You try to nod, but then you hesitate.
「そう　頷こうとして 躊躇してしまう」
「あなたが思い描く理想は 現時点で達成されている社会秩序を
Your own ideals are not clear and well-defined
enough to deny the social order achieved at this point.
否定できるほど明瞭で確固たるものではない」
You recognize that the current peaceful society and harmony
「あなたは　現在の平和な社会を 市民の幸福と秩序による安息を
achieved through law, order, and public
well-being are more important than anything else.
何より重要なものとして認識している」
Hence, no matter how much you hate the
Sibyl System, or how much you wish to bring it down,
「故に　その礎となっているシビュラシステムを
you cannot bring yourself to reject the
system on which all those things are built.
いかに憎悪し　否定しようとも 拒絶することはできない」
Don't talk like you know everything.
知ったような口を利かないで
On the contrary, by analyzing your reactions via cymatic scans, it is easy to grasp your character.
「サイマティックスキャンによる反応を解析すれば
あなたの思考は 全て明確に把握できます」
「虚勢を捨て 腹を割って話し合いましょう」
Please cease this futile posturing
and let us discuss the matter in earnest.
The goal of this meeting is to establish a collaborative relationship.
「この会見の目的は あなたとの協力関係を構築することです」
Collaborative?
協力
CID Division 1 is currently in a state of crisis.
「刑事課一係は　目下のところ 危機的状況にあります」
Due to Kougami Shinya's recklessness and Ginoza Nobuchika's breakdown,
「狡噛慎也の暴走と 宜野座伸元の消耗により
the team is starting to show signs of dysfunction.
チームは機能不全の兆しを見せ始めている」
Unless a new leader takes the initiative in the investigation,
「新たな統率者が 捜査の主導権を握らないかぎり
we cannot expect success in tracking down Makishima Shougo.
槙島聖護の追跡は成果を望めません」
Inspector Ginoza's... breakdown?
宜野座さんが…消耗
Tsunemori Akane. Because you were
caught in an unnecessary inner conflict,
「常守朱」
「あなたもまた 余計な葛藤にとらわれて
you have not been able to exhibit your potential capability either.
本来発揮し得る潜在能力を発揮できていなかった」
Your lack of understanding of the
situation has clouded your judgment.
「状況に対する理解の不足が
あなたの判断力を鈍らせていたのです」
「そこで我々は　特例的な措置として
That is why we decided to make an exception
and reveal to you the truth behind the Sibyl System.
シビュラシステムの真実をあなたに開示しました」
「真相を教えることが あなたという人物にモチベーションを与える上で
We decided that telling you the truth
would be the best way to motivate you.
最善な方法と判断したからです」
Tsunemori Akane...
「常守朱…
You also disagree with Kougami Shinya taking
Makishima Shougo's punishment into his own hands.
あなたも槙島聖護に対する 狡噛慎也の私的制裁を否定している」
You and we both wish to prevent
pointless deaths caused by unchecked emotions.
「あなたも我々も 感情論による無益な犠牲を避けようとしている点で
価値観は共通しています」
私は　槙島の罪が正しく裁かれるべきだと思っているだけ
I only want Makishima's crimes to be judged in a fair and just way.
あなたたちだって 法を犯した前科があるなら
Those among you who broke the law
in the past also need to atone for their crimes.
それに見合った償いをするべきなのよ
Our contributions to society are more than enough
compensation for the damages we caused in the past.
「社会に対する我々の貢献は
過去の被害に対する補償として 充分に過ぎるものです」
都合がいいのね
Isn't that convenient?
Only three minutes left until my future's decided for me.
あと三分で 私の未来も確定か…
This sucks.
憂鬱
Did you do that terribly on the final exam, Yuki?
ゆきってば そこまで最終考査のスコアヤバかったわけ
I couldn't have done worse.
I wonder what kind of job I'll end up with...
もう最悪よ
どんな仕事に就く羽目になるやら…
If we were living in the days before Sibyl existed,
it'd be luck of the draw whether we ended up happy or not.
シビュラ診断のない時代だったら
幸せになれるかどうか運任せだった
So this is a lot better than the old days, at least.
昔に比べたらさ よほどいいじゃん
I envy you. You're likely to end up with multiple aptitudes, Kaori.
佳織は複数適性もらえそうだから いいよね
You can just pick and choose the employer you want.
就職先 より取り見取りじゃん
I'm still nowhere near as good as Akane.
私だって 朱ほどじゃないわよ
Did you see what her score was like?
この子の最終考査 見た
700 points. I can't believe it.
ポイント ７００よ
信じらんない
Well, you know, I've always been lucky when it comes to exams.
あっ昔から 試験のときだけはラッキーなんだよ 私
朱のスコアとサイコパスなら
With your exam results and Psycho-Pass, Akane...
Yeah, you've got a bright future ahead of you.
本当 人生 ばら色よね
I-I do?
そ そんなかな
あっ 来た
Ah! It's here!
Whoa... My rank is "C"...
うわっ Ｃ判定
I knew this would happen, but I'm still shocked.
分かっちゃいたけどショックだわ
Mine are all office jobs. It'll be tough to work my way up from there.
私なんか 事務職ばっか
ここからレベルアップしてくの厳しいな
ねぇねぇ朱は どんなだった
Hey, what did you get, Akane?
Let me see, let me see!
見せて 見せて
うわっ すご 中央省庁全部に適性出てんじゃん
Whoa! Amazing! You've got the necessary
aptitude to work in any of the central ministries!
Wow. That score really is amazing.
ちょっと あんたこのスコア本当にすごいよ
公安局の適性まで出てる
You could even work at the Public Safety Bureau!
で でもさ
B-But... If I've been recommended all these
places, how do I know which one is right for me?
こんなに何から何まで 薦められても
じゃあ結局 どれがいいのか
私 どうやって決めたらいいんだろう
How can I decide?
I don't know. What makes you think
that someone like me would have any idea?
分っかんねえよ
俺なんかに分かるわけねえじゃん
You could become anything.
あんたは何にでもなれた
You could choose any kind of life.
どんな人生を選ぶことだってできた
You've even agonized over it, right?
それで 悩みさえしたんだろ
That's incredible.
すげえよな まるでシビュラができる前のジジババみてえだ
You're just like those old folk who
lived in the days before Sibyl was created.
うん すごいよね
Yeah, it's incredible, isn't it?
誰もが自分の人生を手探りで選んでた
Everyone used to fumble around,
blindly choosing what they were going to do.
それが当たり前の世界があったなんてね
I can't believe that was once our natural way of life.
今じゃシビュラシステムがそいつの才能を読み取って
Nowadays, the Sibyl System reads your talent
and tells you the way of living that will bring you the most happiness.
一番幸せになれる生き方を教えてくれるってのに
本当の人生
And yet, you're talking about your purpose in life?
生まれてきた意味
The reason you were born?
そんなもんで悩むやつがいるなんて
I never even imagined there were
people who stressed over things like that!
考えもしなかったよ
そうだね 重たくてつらい悩みだよ
Yeah, it's tough to deal with. It's always weighing me down.
でもね 今では思うんだ
But... now I feel...
それを悩むことができるって
that being able to worry about those things is what makes me happy.
本当はとても幸せなことじゃないかって
I think the only time people really have
value is when they act according to their own will.
僕はね 人は自らの意志に基づいて行動したときのみ
価値を持つと思っている
So I've asked many people about their true,
repressed desires and observed their actions all this time.
だから 様々な人間に秘めたる意志を問いただし
その行いを観察してきた
そうね あなたの気持ち
Yeah. I think now I can understand how you feel, if only a little.
今なら少しだけ分かるかも
How do you define crime to start with?
そもそも 何を持って犯罪と定義するんだ
With the Dominator you're holding?
君が手にしたその銃
ドミネーターをつかさどるシビュラシステムが決めるのか
Does the Sibyl System that governs that gun decide it?
違うよね それがそもそもの間違いだった
That's wrong, isn't it?
That was the mistake in the first place.
サイマティックスキャンで読み取った生体力場を解析し
By analyzing a bio-organism's force field read by a cymatic scan,
they figure out how a person's mind works.
人の心の在り方を解き明かす
科学の英知はついに魂の秘密を暴くに至り
Science finally discovered the secret behind the human soul,
and this society changed drastically as a result.
この社会は激変した
However, people's wills are not part of that assessment.
だが その判定には人の意志が介在しない
I wonder just what sort of criteria you
use to divide people into good and evil.
君たちはいったい
何を基準に善と悪をより分けているんだろうね
It's not the final judgment of "good" or "evil" that's important.
きっと 大切だったのは
善か悪かの結論じゃない
What matters is that you come to that decision
yourself. That you agonize over it and eventually accept it.
それを自分で抱えて悩んで引き受けることだったんだと思う
I want to bear witness to the splendor of man's soul.
僕は人の魂の輝きが見たい
それが本当に尊いものだと確かめたい
I want to find out once and for all
whether it is truly something worth admiring.
だが己の意志を問うこともせず
However, when humans base their lives around Sybil's Oracle, without ever considering what they really want,
ただ　シビュラの神託のままに生きる人間たちに
果たして価値はあるんだろうか
do they really hold any value?
How could they not?
ないわけないでしょう
あなたが価値を決めるっていうの
Are you saying you can decide if someone has value?
誰かの家族を 友達を
That you can judge the worth of their family and friends?
あなたの知らなかった幸せを
How can you determine the value of happiness you've never felt?!
It was fun and easy. I didn't experience any hardship at all.
面白くって楽ちんで
つらいことなんて何もなかった
全部 誰かに任せっ放しで
Someone else always took care of everything for me, and I never even asked myself what was important.
何が大切なことなのかなんて 考えもしなかった
ねえ 朱
Say, Akane, do you think I was still happy that way?
それでも私は幸せだったと思う
幸せになれたよ
You could have become happy.
You could have searched for the answer anytime.
それを探すことはいつだって できた
生きてさえいれば
Anyone can do it, as long as they're alive.
誰だって
はい 常守です
Hello. Tsunemori speaking.
いったいどこをほっつき歩いていた
Where the hell did you wander off to in a crisis like this?
この非常時に
Ah, well...
あっ えっと
The Chief ordered me to deliver something to the Ministry of Welfare.
局長の命令で ちょっと厚生省まで届け物を
市川で殺人事件だ
There was a murder in Ichikawa.
現場から狡噛の指紋が出た
Kougami's prints have been found at the site. Come here immediately.
すぐに来い
了解です
Okay. I'll be right over.
直ちに急行します
Sibyl System, you can hear me, can't you?
シビュラシステム 聞こえてるんでしょ
あなたたちの言いなりになる上で 一つ条件があるわ
There's something I want in return for what you asked of me.
Please state your request.
伺いましょう
槙島聖護を生きたまま捕らえて連れてきたら
If I bring Makishima Shougo to you, alive,
you will guarantee Kougami Shinya's life in return.
代わりに狡噛慎也の命も保証して
彼の処刑指令を取り下げて
Withdraw his execution order.
Those two things are not logically equivalent.
それは理論的に等価性の成立しない提案です
I don't care about your logic.
あなたたちの理論なんてどうでもいいわ
If Kougami can't be saved, then I'll let Makishima die as well.
狡噛さんが助からないなら
私は槙島も見殺しにする
いざとなればこの手で殺してやる
If push comes to shove, I'll kill him with my own hands.
どう 言いなりにならない私のことも始末する
What are you going to do if I don't obey you?
いいわよ 縢君みたいに殺しなさいよ
Feel free to kill me just like you killed Kagari.
But then you'll have to go find
yourself another pawn you think you can use.
そうして 他に利用できそうな手駒を探すのね
了解しました
Understood.
We will make an exception for Kougami Shinya,
but only once Makishima Shougo is captured alive.
槙島聖護が無事確保された場合に限り
狡噛慎也には特例措置を講じましょう
約束よ
It's a promise, okay?
Hey.
What took you so long?
遅いぞ
I'm sorry. What happened here?
すみません
状況は
Local residents reported seeing someone with that helmet,
近隣住民から例のヘルメットの目撃情報が届いたんでな
いざ聞き込みに回ってみたら
so we asked around a bit.
この家だけセキュリティーがつぶされてた
Then we found out that this house,
and only this house, had been broken into.
で　踏み込んだらこのありさまさ
So we rushed in, only to find this.
被害者は管巻宣昭
The victim's name is Kudama Nobuaki.
He used to work for a lab belonging
to the Ministry of Agriculture and Forestry,
元は農林省管轄の研究所に勤務してましたが
but he retired quite a long time
ago and lived as an ordinary pensioner.
かなり以前に引退して
今は何の変哲もない年金受給者です
家捜しした痕跡の中に狡噛の指紋があった
The house appears to have been
ransacked. We've found Kougami's prints.
しかし 何でまた
But why would he do this?
この首の傷
From the wound on his neck...
槙島聖護の仕業かも
Makishima Shougo might have done this.
Maybe this old man had something
to do with the next stage of Makishima's plan.
この老人が槙島の次の計画に関与していて
それを突き止めた狡噛さんが駆け付けたものの 一歩遅かった
Kougami figured it out and hurried over here, but he was too late.
Kougami really is one step ahead of us, isn't he?
やはり 狡噛が先を行っているってことか
Even so, what possible reason
could Makishima have to kill this geezer?
それにしても
このじいさんがいったいどうして槙島に殺されたのか
ここまで徹底して荒らされた後じゃな
It's hard to investigate a crime scene
that's already been turned inside out.
What do you think Kougami's highest priority would be right now?
狡噛さんが今一番望まない展開は何でしょう
Preventing Makishima from getting away, right?
槙島を取り逃がすことですよね
じゃあ二番目に望まない展開は
Then what would his second highest priority be?
Staying out of our reach until he can kill Makishima, I guess.
槙島を仕留める前に俺たちに見つかること　か
そうですね
Yes. Let's think about things in that order.
その順序で考えましょう
What if Kougami, who got here before us,
had hidden the body somewhere hard to find?
もし 先にこの現場にたどりついた狡噛さんが
死体をどこか見つかりにくい場所に隠していたら
While Kudama Nobuaki remained missing,
管巻宣昭は行方不明のまま
私たちは見当違いの捜索を続け
we would have continued on a wild goose chase,
giving Kougami more of a lead.
さらに差をつけられていた
時間稼ぎにはそれが一番だったはずなんだ
It would've been the best way for him to buy some time.
でも そうしなかった
But he didn't do it.
Kougami isn't the overconfident type.
狡噛さんは自信過剰なタイプじゃない
万が一自分が失敗したときに
He'd account for the possibility that he might fail,
他の誰かが槙島を止められるよう
and leave clues that others could use to stop Makishima.
手掛かりだけは残していったと思います
問題はその手掛かりにいつ気付くか
The question is when we'll pick up on them.
He's testing us.
試されてるんです 私たち
槙島を追うために
Testing our determination to pursue Makishima against his own.
狡噛さんと同じかそれ以上の執念を持っているかどうか
If you lack that determination,
you'll end up stuck here while he goes on ahead.
その覚悟がない人間はここで 足止めされ 出遅れる
喉と両目の傷を集中スキャン
Perform a scan focused on the victim's throat and eyes.
Is there anything there?
何かない
A foreign, metallic object has been detected inside the victim's airway.
被害者の気道内部に金属反応を探知
Gloves.
手袋を
H-Hey, you should leave this to Forensics.
おっ おい 検視に任せろ
それが狡噛さんの時間稼ぎです
That would only increase Kougami's lead.
If we want to catch up with him, we have to do this right now.
追い付こうと思ったら今この場で
Rinse it.
洗浄
It's an audio recording.
音声データですね
元執行官の狡噛だ
This is Kougami, former Enforcer.
このメッセージはもうしばらくしたらやって来るであろう
I'm leaving this message for the
Bureau's detectives when they turn up.
公安局の刑事に向けて残す
あいつ
Damn him!
The victim is Kudama Nobuaki,
a former Doctor of Agricultural Sciences.
被害者は 元農学博士管巻宣昭
He was in charge of the development of the Uka-no-Mitama virus,
ハイパーオーツの疫病対策である
a disease countermeasure for hyper-oats.
ウカノミタマ`ウイルスの開発責任者
日本の完全食料自給に関わる最大の功労者だとされていた
He was considered to be the biggest contributor
to Japan's achievement of complete food autonomy.
槙島聖護は北陸の穀倉地帯を壊滅させるための
Makishima Shougo met with Professor Kudama to learn how to destroy the granary in Hokuriku
何らかのアイデアを管巻教授から引き出しそして殺した
and then killed him.
He gouged out the eyeballs from the victim's
skull and cut off all his fingers at their second joints.
死体は眼球をえぐられ
指は全て第二関節で切断
何らかのセキュリティーを突破するのに必要なのかもしれない
He may have needed them in order
to break through some form of security.
Kudama's old laboratory is an antiquated facility with
biometric-based security instead of the newer cymatic scans.
防犯設備がサイマティックスキャンではなく
まだ旧式の生体認証に頼っていたころの古い施設
おそらくは管巻の研究チームが使っていた
It's located at Izumo University, and the lack of security stands out.
出雲大学のラボが怪しい
現在はウカノミタマ·ウイルスの管理センターに転用されている
This lab is currently used as the
control center for the Uka-no-Mitama virus.
I think that's Makishima's target.
そこが槙島の標的と予想される
He plans to destroy the whole granary?
穀倉地帯の壊滅
Does he intend to commit bio-terrorism all on his own?
単独でバイオテロだと
Let's hurry. We still have time.
急ぎましょう
今ならまだきっと間に合います
You'll never walk alone
Anata to iku
I walk with you
Donna tsumi mo
I will share all your sins
Seotte ageru
Michi naki michi wo
Together with you
Aruiteku no
I walk
Anata to
I will stay with you
Anata no te de
Hold me in your arms
Dakishimete yo
Hold me as tight as you can
Omoikkiri
Nozomenai mono wa
I could wish for anything
Nani mo nai kara
All alone with you
Anata to futari de
Well then... Shall I get started?
さて 始めようか
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".